

ZAMIR SHAMS

FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER

CONTACT INFO

- (+39) 3279984850
- zamir.shams2014@gmail.com
- ← Spartan Shams AN
- Q Zamir Shams
- 9 83050 AV Italy

SKILLS

JAVASCRIPT
CSS
BOOTSTRAP
HTML
SASS
RWD
WEB
LASS
PS

LANGUAGES

ENGLISH ITALIAN HINDI PERSIAN

REFERENCES

DANIELE

SAI Project Head

(+39) 3283419801

sprarxsantangelo@gmail.com

JAWAD MUSHTAQ

Web Developer

(+93) 3533703754

jawa.mushtaq111@gmail.com

EDRIS MALYA

Senior Developer

(+93) 781357171

Edris.malya@gmail.com

ABOUT ME

I am a Front-end web developer in Italy. I have a serious passion for UI effects, animations and creating intutive, dynamic user experience. Well-organized person, problem solver, independent employee with high attention to details.

Since beginning my journey as a freelance developer nearly 3 years ago, I've done remote work for agencies, consulted for startups, and collaborated with talented people to create digital products for both business and consumer use.

EXPERIENCE

RANA UNIVERSITY

2018 - 2019

RANA UNIVERSITY

2019 - 2020

MFNDU

2020 - 2021

EDUCATION

G.H KHAN HIGH SCHOOL

1999 - 2011

UTT. TECH UNIVERSITY INDIA

7/2014 - 12/2015

RANA UNIVERSITY

4/2017 - 3/2021

AWARDS

SANDHURST MEDAL OF UK GOV

ian 2017

TOP RUNNER INSTRUCTOR

jan 2017

INTERN

Assisting in troubleshooting issues on webbased systems, updating and edit website content, posts and pages. Provide technical support related to web-based systems to internal teams.

JUNIOR WEB DEVELOPER

As Junior Web Developer working with a team of developers to create websites and applications. I have been working under the supervision of senior developers in software department as involved in all stages of the project, from brainstorming to final testing.

FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER

Being responsible for the design and construction of websites. ensuring that sites meet user expectations by ensuring they look good, run smoothly and offer easy access points with no error messages.

SCHOOL

School gives a chance for me to acquire knowledge on various fields of education such as literature, English, mathematics, math, and other numerous subjects.

MANAGEMENT, NETWORK

I leraned an overall knowledge of defense management also networking fundamentals, protocols, traffic, security, and communication principles.

COMPUTER SCIENCE (B.S.E)

We coverd theory of computation, fundamentals of C.S, compliers, operating systems, basic programming, architecture, web, databases, algorithms and data structures.

EXCELLENT WORK

Excellence is potential chiseled into a more perfect state through vision, dedication and determination, I have gotten the Sandhurst medal of United Kingdom.

OUTSTANDING PERFORMANCE

As a result of excellent work among the team its really proud to gain the top score of the team due to excellent work.

Copyright© SPARTAN-PROGRAMMER